[{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":12935,"timeElapsed":108034},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980334933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":12352,"timeElapsed":120388},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":9348,"timeElapsed":129740},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980352828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":8542,"timeElapsed":138283},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980360305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7475,"timeElapsed":145760},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980369319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9012,"timeElapsed":154774},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980395233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":25912,"timeElapsed":180688},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":16890,"timeElapsed":197580},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5791,"timeElapsed":203373},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":9614,"timeElapsed":215275},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":6490,"timeElapsed":221767},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":10236,"timeElapsed":232005},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3511,"timeElapsed":235517},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980454308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4243,"timeElapsed":239762},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980457751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3442,"timeElapsed":243206},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3632,"timeElapsed":246840},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7625,"timeElapsed":254467},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980476588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7575,"timeElapsed":262043},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":9935,"timeElapsed":274186},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980492510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3777,"timeElapsed":277965},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9415,"timeElapsed":287382},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2786,"timeElapsed":290170},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5585,"timeElapsed":295756},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":6151,"timeElapsed":301908},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5795,"timeElapsed":307705},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980529215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6963,"timeElapsed":314670},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980532316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3100,"timeElapsed":317771},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":12061,"timeElapsed":331919},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":6034,"timeElapsed":337955},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562379,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9878,"timeElapsed":347834},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":6136,"timeElapsed":353972},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4158,"timeElapsed":358132},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980577381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4703,"timeElapsed":362836},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980581438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4057,"timeElapsed":366893},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4335,"timeElapsed":371229},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980591880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6104,"timeElapsed":377335},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2818,"timeElapsed":380154},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":11138,"timeElapsed":393312},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980612091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4232,"timeElapsed":397546},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4585,"timeElapsed":402133},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980619548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2868,"timeElapsed":405003},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4828,"timeElapsed":409832},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980628518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4139,"timeElapsed":413973},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3768,"timeElapsed":417743},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980638266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5976,"timeElapsed":423721},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3677,"timeElapsed":427400},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":11227,"timeElapsed":440686},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980657887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2655,"timeElapsed":443342},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5432,"timeElapsed":448775},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2850,"timeElapsed":451627},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3456,"timeElapsed":455084},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4066,"timeElapsed":459152},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980677549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3850,"timeElapsed":463003},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980681664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4114,"timeElapsed":467119},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980687128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5462,"timeElapsed":472583},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692699,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5569,"timeElapsed":478153},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980704319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":9793,"timeElapsed":489774},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980708159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3839,"timeElapsed":493614},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4110,"timeElapsed":497726},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980715527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3254,"timeElapsed":500982},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980719711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4183,"timeElapsed":505166},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980722379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2666,"timeElapsed":507834},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980725518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3137,"timeElapsed":510973},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5568,"timeElapsed":516542},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4622,"timeElapsed":521166},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980753947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":16401,"timeElapsed":539402},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2912,"timeElapsed":542316},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980764416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":7553,"timeElapsed":549871},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2664,"timeElapsed":552536},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980770245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3162,"timeElapsed":555700},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980773468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3222,"timeElapsed":558923},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980777486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4017,"timeElapsed":562941},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980784530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7042,"timeElapsed":569985},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980787259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2727,"timeElapsed":572714},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":8653,"timeElapsed":583379},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2646,"timeElapsed":586027},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980809225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":8652,"timeElapsed":594680},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2793,"timeElapsed":597474},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4697,"timeElapsed":602173},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980822125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":5405,"timeElapsed":607579},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980829755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":7629,"timeElapsed":615210},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980833853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4096,"timeElapsed":619308},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2578,"timeElapsed":621888},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5073,"timeElapsed":628795},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980845849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2508,"timeElapsed":631304},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980849772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3921,"timeElapsed":635227},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980852239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":2466,"timeElapsed":637694},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980855874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3632,"timeElapsed":641328},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980864972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":9097,"timeElapsed":650427},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980869436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4462,"timeElapsed":654891},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980874320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4883,"timeElapsed":659775},{"subjectID":"asaldl8rp5","prolificID":"5b0710e7a84dcf0001beee8a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26564633b6f44f3f120","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980877164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2842,"timeElapsed":662619}]